[Music]
my name is michelle pfeiffer fennecs i'm
an investment manager from the
investment team and I supervise Francis
our intern forward together project
brought in my perspective this is the
first time that we really hired him with
a perspective of this will work no
matter what communication barrier there
is he helped the team a lot not only on
the reporting but he also helped on the
daily operations of our team it's really
nice that we gave this a chance to work
with Francis
my name is Spice Paris I'm an associate
manager with people in culture team we
have two interns what they do on a daily
basis is they help us in organising the
different records that we have in people
in culture tinta christine she can
follow instructions easily diana is very
cheerful as well I there were times when
I needed to prepare for the team
building or team development of the IT
team I just gave her instructions and
she was able to execute that I find that
those two girls are very focused as well
and they can do their jobs well
[Music]
[Applause]